<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-12-16T17:47:13-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Your awesome title</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Reflecting on NeurIPS 2023</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/12/16/neurips2023" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Reflecting on NeurIPS 2023" /><published>2023-12-16T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-12-16T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/12/16/neurips2023</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/12/16/neurips2023"></content><author><name>Andrew Ye</name></author><category term="artificial-intelligence" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Purpose of This Blog</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/12/14/firstpost" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Purpose of This Blog" /><published>2023-12-14T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-12-14T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/12/14/firstpost</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/12/14/firstpost">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/blogging.png&quot; alt=&quot;xkcd 741&quot; style=&quot;display:block; margin-left:auto; margin-right:auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: bold&quot;&gt;Figure 1:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&quot;font-style: italic&quot;&gt;Blogging&lt;/span&gt;  by xkcd&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The art of writing has spanned milennia, yet the practice of blogging – personal subspaces for the public – is a rather recent development. With the emergence of the internet and its ability to offer easily accessible and public personal spaces, it seemed natural for people to begin jotting their thoughts down in this environment. Such a form of quick, unbounded, and (hopefully) quality prose is one in which I recently have decided to delve into. While I generally consider myself a capable writer, I find that I tend to produce “quality” only after several rounds of methodical deliberation. This is fine, but what I would &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; like to develop is a quick sense of what to write and how to write it. In this manner, I consider this blog as that medium to develop the skill of being able to efficiently communicate in well-phrased and educative process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with any skill, repetition is key. I anticipate that my first few posts will read quite lackluster. However, the eventual goal is that such capabilities scale with the amount of work invested. I also certainly hope that one doesn’t misinterpret the desire for fast writing with sloppy writing. Rest assured, all of my posts will have been proofread multiple times, and I will be careful to cite relevant sources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of content itself, expect most of the writings here to be primarily related to my work (artificial intelligence, mathematics, computer science, and finance) and written in a fairly technical and/or philosophical manner (I will often attempt to relate the two). However, I may write every now and then about subjects like art, film, and other facets that spark my interests. Any research explorations that are too short for a full-fledged paper will also be housed here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, I will briefly touch on how this website was made. The site itself is stored via &lt;a href=&quot;https://pages.github.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;github pages&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; is used for static content generation. Everything else is a mixture of custom css and html, much of which was directly inspired (if not copied) from Gregory Gundersen’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://gregorygundersen.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt;, of whose minimalistic and pleasing designs I fell in love with after stumbling upon his article on &lt;a href=&quot;https://gregorygundersen.com/blog/2020/04/11/moments/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;moments&lt;/a&gt;, which I highly recommend for anyone interested in probability distributions. Although I expect my website’s design to gradually change and develop its own identity, it currently stands as a near carbon copy of his, to which I am eternally thankful for the following words of his:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center; font-style: italic&quot;&gt;&quot;Feel free to copy my website.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Andrew Ye</name></author><category term="other" /><summary type="html">Figure 1: Blogging by xkcd</summary></entry></feed>